do you want to rock you sit down and you
have a foot problem
oh man that's nice you ever poop with a
foot bro no hired that's the proper way
to poop though that's the proper way to
poop there we go who'd you hear that
from you just talk to people who know
the proper way so that yeah exactly that
my doctor told me your doctor told me I
don't even have a doctor health
insurance I went to the doctor for the
first time in quite a while a couple
days ago and it went pretty well we had
a good talk about like ADHD ADHD
medication Thanks depression medication
is pretty cool
it seems so weird to talk to them about
that because they seem they seem like
they're uh I don't know kind of hesitant
there's always stigmas based on like
medication that people get and like you
know if they prescribed opioids or
something like that most people will say
okay but then when they get the skeptics
that come up and talk to them and say
like like do you actually believe in
this and like do you know what this does
to my body and I starts doing that I
feel like that must be so daunting for
people because they're just doing what
they're told that day we're just like
they're following a script in there like
I mean to the best of their ability
they're they're doing their jobs yeah
absolutely
yeah they they I'm it's not like they
have answers that like like to all their
to everyone's problems mhm
it's not like doctors just consult
everything for everyone yeah and that's
they're taking on a mass amount of
people and they need something that's
gonna help someone fast like obviously
if you get to spend one like one doctor
got to spend time with one patient only
I'm sure there's other ways of like
helping someone through their their
problems or whatever it may be but it's
like you got a hundred thousand people
coming up to you sure and I'm like yup
just [__] cranking the well here's
what's gonna work best for your ASAP
alright there you go there's some Prozac
yeah it is so weird it's funny we just
kind of were like well that's just how
it is
mm-hmm in like I don't have an answer
for how to make it better but it seems
like there should be something different
it seems like there should be something
it's in us there and yeah but I
definitely think we're slipping into a
different age in a different time yeah
like with holistic medicine yeah yeah
it's just crazy like how we went from
kind of knowing a lot about the earth as
a people and as a society if you look
back in time and then slowly that just
like fades away from generation to
generation now we're here now and we're
like all right we have this massive
amount of technology and science and
we're like we can create medicines and
do all this [__] but now you got people
that are looking back like dude
everything's already here like one of
the biggest cures for PTSD is now
mushrooms and psychedelics in because
it's like it's a proof for human testing
all over now it's it's like on stage
three of human trials for like PTSD yeah
or no wait maybe that's MDMA right now
it's MDMA and but psychedelics are like
right behind it I had this at this point
documentary on Netflix that just came
out about it there's just a lot of
documentaries coming out about it now
but that's cool like you were saying
earlier it's like a cute sorry actual
scientists are now talking about the
benefits of psychedelics in like
psychotherapy is just crazy like aren't
you just supposed to give me pills and
like to say I'll be better but like
you're asking me to trip balls
you're asking me to like battle my
consciousness and myself what is good
past so what do you think is gonna
happen a to me it seems like the
craziest fastest thing happening ever as
in like I feel like in the next 10 20
years I don't know timelines right well
but like there's gonna be clinics where
you're like all right well I'm gonna go
stay the night in this place and trip my
[__] face off and melt
go and hopefully solve some traumas I'll
see you in two days you know like I
think that's gonna be a normal thing
what do you think what's the what's the
next 10 20 years for like the future of
like let's say healing and psychedelics
and I think that's the exact path that
we are gonna go on like it only seems
natural that if we commit to making any
of this legal which peyote and mushrooms
are legal in now Nevada and some parts
of Oakland Oakland arresting man I'm in
California but you don't want just geeks
off the street going and taking [__]
peyote and going in the middle of the
street and like you know like those
aren't the right circumstances and like
that would just be crazy for the
government to be like all right go take
peyote we got it at 7-eleven and you go
in just 13 and that's on the street like
no so we're gonna have complete control
over it there's gonna be guided leaders
through your journey trip sitters trip
sitters that are professionals that do
this every day yeah awesome
like what what are what our trip centers
for anybody who doesn't know what's a
trip Center a trip sitter is basically a
shaman who leads you in the right
direction and keeps you calm and
centered because when you do these
things by yourself you're gonna be
battling parts of your mind parts of
your body things that usually make you
extremely uncomfortable that you would
run from or date you would normally run
from but these things making you defend
you yes yes and it makes you it makes
you face them you have no option you're
taking me so that you actually cannot
run anywhere because it's internal and
you face them and it's really
overwhelming for so many people
including myself like anytime I do it
I'm like it's it's a scary thing of
course um yeah so you don't want to be
just on the side of the road or just
like at some party doing anything
yeah no it's just so they have trip
sitters people who know what they're
doing it and they help you out
yeah and that's what's so powerful about
these psychedelics and these experiences
it is a way in which it's just making
you face yourself and your truths and
for a lot of the reasons that people
take it obvious like PTSD and certain
traumas and things like that it's the
number one underlining thing is you hear
stories of people in war and they can't
get over the war they can't get over
people and their friends dying and
that's their only way to live is to live
through the experience of remembering
their friends and remembering the days
but it haunts them at the same time and
they just can't face it well this makes
you face it with help you know with help
from a leader shaming a person who's
really really really going to balance
you and let you know that you are gonna
be okay because most people they're just
ended alone
they have PTSD and no one understands
mm-hmm like I mean they are they they
can't even yeah they can't understand it
them is something we're just as a as a
collective starting to like find ways to
actually help people you know instead it
is Shepherd yeah yeah it's just clear
its its clarity no in the Fox what do
you think the next cuz cuz that's how it
is you know now but as they become legal
there's gonna be new you know
government-funded sure yeah
some places whatever however it works
but there's also gonna be new types of
like retreats that are gonna pop up all
over the all over the you know world
potentially it's so much to the u.s. if
it's legalized that are gonna be like
you're like alright they're almost to be
like little burning a man's of sorts
it's not gonna be as intense but I don't
know what that's what I think what do
you think over the next again 10 20
years as like the Western culture
develops some sort of like [__] starts
popping up to where we can heal people
with psychedelics it's gonna be a
business thing it's gonna have to be one
of those businesses look like yeah
that's what's so hard about it too is
because when you take these things you
are so far away from the thought of our
society and like business and the way
that the world runs like you're so much
more focused on the way in which you
treat yourself the way in which you
treat others just kind of it corrects
you and checks you and point out your
flaws and helps you realize how to
counteract those and as far as it goes
in like a business sense I think it's
gonna be a lot more humbling of a
society if it begins to emerge the way I
want it to if it begins to really take
over and have a foundation like I
believe weed does now it's believed by
so much amount of the population at this
point that we're gonna see a shift in
greed and a shift in just I don't know
this selfish way no this yeah you know
the selfish ways of society of living
yeah this is like dog-eat-dog world that
we think we have to this is the only
option yeah and I think it's that's what
the big success is about it is that it
checks your flaws but it also makes you
yearn for a true sense of community and
people and I think people are gonna
become more drawn to people instead of
drawn to technology or whatever the case
may be I don't know I think it just has
a lot of positive benefits if used
correctly if used incorrectly which
obviously it's gonna have its flaws
they're people you can't trust with we'd
still to like there's people that smoke
weed and do it for medical purposes they
do it for peaceful purposes or just you
know creativity or whatever and then
there's people that just change smoke
all day long and just stay high and do
nothing in
to run from their problems yeah yeah
yeah yeah second office for see right
through that one yeah so you know
speaking of community connecting people
and bringing people together Brandon
welcome to the junkie I love Bob keep
going so just were like in the middle of
talking about psilocybin or something
yeah I'm super pumped to have you here
man we've we haven't been friends for a
very long time but we've been you know
we had like this cool friend a friend
connection
we got linked up through a couple other
Creators and now like there's a lot of
wild production and junkyard love stuff
in the works each of our companies so
yeah it's gonna be it's this is just the
beginning so suddenly decided thank you
for having me on appreciate it
yeah I'm pumped always have you here um
it's funny cuz we've hung out multiple
times or like yeah man hey bro it'll be
cool to meet you let's link up yeah
let's podcast we can find out like they
were supposed to be like a meetup to
podcast and we ended up just being like
12 year old BFFs who just cuz there's a
bug on each other and like dude we did
we just quit really well the mind bombs
yeah bro we're just like talking about
consciousness within like 30 minutes of
meeting each other and we ran it you
know we go out in the woods we just run
run around and meditate do yoga vlogs
and [__] it was cool man I feel like
we've got a good vibe so it's it's gonna
be fun to have you on the podcast and
for me to be on your podcast as well
likewise you know because because you
and I really we we extend our thoughts
you know past ourselves and we talked
about intricate things and a lot of
times if like we stumble upon things
that are like wow this is this is an
important subject let's actually let's
let's take a moment and you know put a
little peg in this mm-hmm
so I think that it's important um you
know I I kind of project outwardly you
you know tell people not to be a coward
and to like follower their intuition and
and do what's right and so I think that
airing these conversations whether or
not sometimes they're going to be maybe
we're going to talk about farting or
whatever
doesn't matter but I think sometimes we
do stumble upon some important things
that a lot of listeners would benefit so
I think it's a it's a good
responsibility of us as we've talked
about outside of this podcast to to you
know get some bit on audio and continue
talking about these some things so yeah
I think I mean both of us have obviously
perspective on our side of life and I
mean I feel like in these times we share
a lot of qualities of a lot of other
people our age who are going through the
same things it's it's a time like just
like you talk to your parents
and they can all relate and say remember
the time when you know the life kind of
felt like this or life kind of felt like
that things like that I feel like we
understand what is going on in our
generation and in our lifetime and we
can connect with a lot of people in a
lot as it's happening right drops are
going to me is this happening to you is
it happening to us as a whole and so I
think it's I think it's cool that we
actually can sit down and talk about it
and analyze from different perspectives
yeah yeah dude it's cool and I think
it's again important I think it's
important for anybody who's like hey
I've been kind of scared to to talk up
you know like don't don't got megaphone
and staying on on the corner and start
yelling but you know do you have thought
about it yeah you always want to but
it's so easy to start a podcast you need
to you know spend a couple days spend a
couple of hours YouTube it Google if you
have if you feel the same thing that we
feel like hey these are important
conversations they might help somebody
up dude start a podcast very encouraging
to start a podcast so speaking of
different perspectives my perspective
from here Pacific Northwest
I've always been born and raised here
this is where I'm from you are here now
you and you and Lacey I live just down
in Portland Oregon and you guys it's
super love it now I know that but so
would you mind giving me just like a
little bit of maybe like your background
like your move over here maybe a little
about what what's going on with your
company
okay well I moved from Phoenix Arizona
where it's ungodly hot and it's pretty
dry and flat and I love to travel I love
to hike I took on a lot of that scene so
I felt like that was a part of my life
that just was complete or mostly
complete and I feel like I just wanted
to grow in a different way the Pacific
Northwest is a very creative place from
what I've seen online I've been here I
love the vibe the energy that people
just I mean like meeting you you have
been an amazing person and there's
something different about the places you
live and the people that live there and
it was just a fresh perspective for me
on on meeting you meeting people like
you immediately and just getting hooked
on becoming open and becoming creative
and not letting you know my ego or
whatever holding me back from my
creativity or what I want to say or how
I feel and things like that so that's a
big reason why we moved I love nature
too so I mean hikes and everything are
beautiful it's I mean I can walk outside
and it's I feel like I'm already like
outdoors the outdoors so yeah Brahman be
honest you're sitting on that side I'm
sitting on this side because I can
glance out the window as I'm thinking as
I'm talking to you you know you get a
look at some lights I don't even care
give that didn't that look so yeah but
so we may see it so you moved over from
Arizona yeah we got linked up through
our friend Jessica she moved over there
you guys yeah she moved over there I met
my fiancee
yeah and then they moved back then we
moved back and the rest is history
yeah is it so cool like you follow on
like you're like you just know if this
person is pretty cool I can just vibe
with them and fill myself with them and
you follow that and then you know the
way that life works out you didn't think
this way when you're 16 but all of a
sudden man I know some cool people oh
I've met them because of this person who
knows this person who knows this person
yeah and it's just so crazy like tennis
shoes
she always said like I can't wait for
you to meet Jake I can't wait like you
guys are gonna hit it off you guys are
like just alike and all this stuff like
like I just know it I know what I know
it I know it and then like from my
perspective I'm all obviously like yeah
I'd love to meet him like I don't I
don't feel like I've met a bunch of
people that I'm like I have to like
surround myself with them and I have to
pick their brain and I have to share my
creativity's and things like that with
them and my thoughts and stuff and and
so I was just like all right yeah yeah
I'll meet him um and then I met you and
I was like just blown away like you just
like are everywhere and I and everything
I drove that's what I thought about you
as this guy [__] understands he
understands in the way that he he
explains to me what he's thinking about
I'm like dude I know what you're saying
it's it's it's just very I don't know I
have it very clear and vivid when I when
we converse it just seems like we
understand each other you know even if
no one on this podcast does sorry
yeah he was in Alaska it's big I get you
guys like you guys you guys are funny my
name is awesome Brannon my middle name
is Jake it's weird I like it they call
me Brandon Jake yeah
I'm BJ dammit yeah anyway hey leading in
from a bj joke let's actually just jump
into something that popped in my mind do
it that's so hilarious but actually
something that I think might be a little
bit important a little bit strange talk
about it first but um the bromance so
like I have grown up in you know this
area is a mill smaller town and so I
grew up with kind of like I was wearing
skinny pants like a punk rock I wear
eyeliner for a while it would always be
called gay all these things anyway you
know it'd be a joke a lot of the part
and I get that and I understood like
there's kind of big dummies whatever
yeah but as you get older you realize
you're like oh man those things kind of
did affect my decision yeah and then so
you get into relationships and I'm just
very you know I grew up I
a lot of older sisters a lot of women
that have been around me as I was
growing up I'm just more intact with my
emotions I guess then a lot of other
guys and so as we're talking as we're
sharing these things I feel like I
inherently have this like old little
habit way back in the back of my head
that I'm not really responding to
anymore but of like like I'm always like
a little embarrassing that you're being
so loud about the bromance thing they're
like you're like oh this is a dude don't
like remember and it's so fun needs to
call you gay and these yeah all this
stuff for expressing yourself right yeah
it's so silly and I think it's just
worth I think it's might be worth
talking about like how silly that really
is just pointing it out for one so if
you know let's say there's a younger
listener that might be like you know
like dude I love my friend like I love
him like a nightlight but people call me
gay like I know I'm not gay like yeah
you know look look inside yourself in if
you have you know these things like
there's a whole process of understanding
if you're gay I'm sure if you really
think that you're gay you can really go
through that process but like if you
know like no of course I'm not I just I
really like this guy it's so ok and I
think that in our world it's hard to
like assess that and talk about it and
so a lot of times friendships go
unappreciated like there's there's this
when two dudes get super blacked-out
drunk you can see there's a lot of
hugging like bro I appreciate you but I
think I'm someone a lot of my friends I
think hear the same way that like I
don't have to have a single drop of me
to like give you a sincere hug like bro
I really appreciate your friendship yeah
I appreciate your conversation I
appreciate this about you I'm so glad
that we connected cool yeah I think it
should be they should be open up what do
you think about that like did you ever
have any experience growing up Brendan
about like being uncomfortable with like
saying I love you to another male figure
let's say yes and that's funny that you
said that I was literally just thinking
about this the other week because I feel
so comfortable now in expressing myself
in ways that I used to be so scared to
do because the people you care about
most mainly are the ones that will tell
you you're gay or like you look gay or
yeah you're just not following the
trends of society or fashion or like
you're trying something new
like they don't like it at first and
that I think is what hurt me the most
and degraded me the most I got here mom
my brother called me gay for wearing
skinny jeans like super skinnies or he
would call me gay for like just trying
something new or my dad would be like
why did you why are you wearing that
like why are you doing this stuff like
yeah I think it does look funky at it
like I'm just trying it like right oh I
kind of want to see how I feel in it I
kind of want to see if this is my if
this is my my job you know like but the
trick that I learned after a while of
just kind of hiding my feelings and kind
of brushing it off and not letting it
affect me anymore was repetition and
saying like this is cool to me so there
was like say I wore some skinny jeans
and my brother came in and was like what
the [__] are you wearing like that looks
so gay right now you're wearing super
skinnies I would literally be like I
don't know man I feel fresh as [__]
right now I feel great right and dude
that's in his house yeah any second one
so he's like you really think so you
really think so my gay if you really
look at me like what's this trend hit
like just saying that just cuz it's like
just to see if I can win in any sort of
way and then after a while you know I
have repetitively say that like if you
if he sees me again oh you're wearing
those jeans again yeah these are
freshers [__] man I can't take them off
these are so cool becomes a habit you
just know - yeah boom and then all of a
sudden you see him kind of change like I
see him now and I see like where his
thought is my damn bows are actually
kind of emerging yeah maybe I'll wear
those and then you go out and I'm
wearing them and like his friends will
see me wearing them and kind of like
look and then he'll hit me on the
shoulder and go bro check these out
these are fresh as [__] he's on a new
wave he's trying something new and
that's how I got over it I got over it
by even if I didn't fully believe that
I'd either look good in it or wanted to
act a certain way or
try this new thing I believe that I
wanted to and absolutely that belief
system is winning and repetition in that
belief system it's constantly pushing
yourself it's going to fight back you're
gonna have tension but you can say
something a million times a million
just repetitively not annoyingly but
just confident and people believe it
they start to become attracted to the
idea you believe it they believe it yeah
I mean that's that's in you you've got
to believe it then I'm to believe it I
mean if you're and that's kind of where
we get a little self-conscious if it's
like aha you know what we're in the
mirror if you don't amp yourself up
enough yeah and you let other people
like oh those are silly and you know and
you're like oh help me with your stupid
you're just walking around feeling dumb
leg doll day mm-hmm you know you gotta
you gotta have that confidence like
going to the mirror and you can give
yourself the old finger gun yeah you
look pretty good it might have to be a
reason and it's not about good you know
comparatively it's about I feel like
this is this is a little bit of me like
it I feel like this feels nice you know
I like the way these pants look on me
mm-hmm
and you just imagine it like you would
feel overjoyed if you had borne
something and you walked outside and you
saw someone wearing the exact same
outfit or something very close and
resemblance to it and if you guys hit it
off and said oh I had the same mutual
you know hobbies and things like that
like I love to skate our escape choosin
mm-hmm a dress like a skate or whatever
like you just met a friend and that
makes you extremely happy there's just
because you don't follow the same trends
and vibes as everyone else doesn't mean
that there's not someone else out there
that's trying to do the same thing as
you keep showing who you are so that
others can find people like you and
that's you create a bond and a
friendship it's if you're hiding who you
are you're never gonna find people that
are like you because they might be
hiding who they are and if you're
constantly hiding just to follow what
makes everyone else happy when they only
see you for a split second of their day
what's the point of that that's
beautiful I like the way you put that
that's good yeah it it's it's a thing
that's really it's a big misconception I
think society right now is uh it's
getting better but the lack of being
confident in oneself mm-hmm is it's sad
that that I've fallen victim to it too
but it said that people actually change
their life and change their thought
process and their perspectives and kind
of degrade themselves because they're
not doing what's cool to someone else
all right you know it's not fair it
doesn't make any sense you know and it
was like wait like you're choosing
someone else's version of yes over your
version of yes yeah like even though
it's like somewhere in my heart like
that little voice that says like I want
those pants I bought them because I want
to wear them mm-hmm I think that's the
voice that's true that's truth yes
that's real that's the real voice not
like the popular girl who says the ears
fast who wears spazzy red pants whatever
it might be and that's what's so that's
it really hurts when you know someone
especially that you care about degrades
you in such a way and they have that
power like you don't understand how much
power and just conviction you have over
someone just by telling them hey like I
don't like that you look stupid or
whatever they just made me that that is
ultimate power over someone's mind your
mind controlling your manipulating their
thoughts and their ideas when they're
already confused on what their did
people are trying to figure themselves
out they don't know that's everyone's
problem I don't know I feel like I don't
know myself I feel like I I'm lost I
feel like I'm all this stuff it's a gray
bar because there's so many people that
are constantly manipulating your path on
who you perceive yourself to be right
telling you that you're someone other
than than what you are they're they're
they're allowing
the the they're telling the Sun to be
more like the moon mm-hmm
you know so I was thinking as you're
saying that I actually have this friend
grape bush can't wait for you to meet
them um this this friend group that
threw some cool circumstances like led
to like random Twitter followers through
friends of friends and I was in EDC
Vegas with a friend and essentially
these people who live up in Seattle now
my Seattle friends now they were also in
Vegas at EDC we hadn't met we only had
one I only had one Gabi on Twitter
mm-hmm anyway it was like hey Wade
mutual friends I have you on Twitter you
want to meet up with us and we're like
yeah like ended up being really cool
really cool friends sprouted this
wonderful friendship I started traveling
we started doing Coachella together
every year anyway so I started to feel I
got this feeling when I'd hang out with
them and like I felt so much like myself
thank you I felt so comfortable you know
we'd go to festivals so you kind of like
dress up extra I really always like
dressing up and festivals and stuff you
know but what they would do is you would
wake up like everybody's like drinking
the night before you know everybody
wakes up kind of hungover whatever but
still all the girls all the guys good
morning like how do you sleep like
here's a glass of water and then you
start getting ready and they're like I
love that top or like like all those
shoes look good or like you look
beautiful today like your skin's glowing
like it's it's compliments but they're
true they're sincere like it's they
genuinely care they're like I love this
person next to me we had a wonderful
time last night
I generally love this thing about them
you come out with this outfit and
they're like that looks so cool they
talk to you about it break it down it
started like it was weird because I
hadn't really experienced that I think
my friends and I had had this know like
oh that's cool let go that's cool man or
whatever like a casual kind of a man
like huh sort of interaction but I don't
know these people
I know it's just clothes you know extent
to other compliments but just
complimenting someone can do so much and
it could also shine a light on the fact
that the opposite of a compliment making
fun of what someone is choosing to do or
where whatever
this is super painful especially at a
young age it's hard you know in in the
joking has to be clear that it's a joke
it has to be a joke to both parties or
it's not entirely a joke and a lot of
times you don't have to change who you
are if you're joking person but a lot of
times it's just one conversation away
you know someone's making funny just
gonna have that conversation and there's
just uh I think people don't understand
the difference between a degrading
remark and just talking [__] with a
friend you know and just like kind of BS
in them and making a joke about it what
I find is that a lot of people will kind
of hide their remarks behind a BS sort
of stance in a way that they approach
the situation like well so they go look
your pants look stupid man you look down
and like laugh at it and then that's
supposed to be that or like dude you
look [__] gay and then leave it at
that and then leave it's like common
phrase growing up yeah and then but you
don't realize it like every time you
like walked around them and they kind of
made fun of it just poked a little bit
those pokes add up and then you go home
and you're like am i portraying myself
as like a gay man like mm I is are you
because I'm not gay but I don't want
people to think I'm gay exactly yeah
yeah and it's like you
there's BS and then there's the BS turns
to degrading and it's I find that so
much in a lot of the ways that people
treat each other it's like it's just it
to them it feels like nothing it's just
a small jab
to to other people it's sometimes a
genuine debacle yeah but if you get
[__] jabbed if you got a job in the
face you're gonna feel it like obviously
it's not the strongest punch you get jab
20 times in the face you're gonna be
hurting pretty bad and you're gonna be
pretty pissed at least a little confused
a little disoriented [__] am I so here's
the thing though is here's the the
incorrect
analysis of that is too like wood you
can't ever joke with anybody and just
gotta be look everybody in the face and
say you love them and like some people
aren't like that but I think that there
needs to be of course emotional
intelligence to know that this person is
joking but I think that there needs to
be I know a among humor among like the
typical man-to-man
teasing thing mm-hmm there's got to be
some more clarity some more I don't know
some some more level ground between cuz
we've got to be able to have comedy
comedy is the most important thing we've
got I would have poked fun at each other
we've got a I guess what we need to do
is as individuals we need to get better
at reading they're like you know so like
if I'm an uncle and I'm poking fun at my
nephew about something I need to look
down and be like he doesn't like that
dude he's he's clearly like
uncomfortable and he doesn't like that
joke you need to be aware of what you're
saying like and so I use that example
just because I have nephews now and I
feel like back on my head I remember
like uncle's jokingly calling me gay or
something but I think that the the jokes
they got to be available right like
we've got to be able to make fun but so
how do you how do you just gotta get
better at reading people's body language
and motions I guess yeah but I mean
obviously that is like number one but I
feel like the it's tough cuz you have to
joke like you have that's gonna come out
it's just what happens with guys what
happens with us like I do it too I think
the problem is that like once people
recognize it they almost kind of shell
up and they I don't I only know from my
perspective and I know that if I did
that someone and it has happened and I
look back I didn't say anything to them
like I'm sorry or maybe I took that too
far or whatever and just kind of made it
a better situation a lot of people will
just kind of bottle it up and then take
it with them and then that gonna hurt
them too
it kind of puts a weird damper on your
guys's relationship I mean obviously
things bounce back immediately if it's
someone you love but if it's some random
person and I hope no random person is
just going out there just talking [__]
to you because I feel like that is crazy
think I just did most respect to people
who I don't know at all and tongue [__]
that's that's how the world should be
you gotta treat every respect first and
foremost yeah all right well so we
talked about bromance
so overall friends it's okay that
romance it's okay yeah appreciate
friendship I'm glad we met we're just
giving nickels over there we just
knocked it up let's talk about I want to
get just like a little bit of an
overview and then right afterwards feel
free let's dive into whatever you you
had wanted to discuss but I do want to
give a little rundown what's what's wild
productions what's what's your company
wow the productions is a media
production agency right now specializing
in weddings corporate commercials and
things like that but I do want to begin
to move into the movie scene short films
things like that and I feel like my
strong suit is actually relaying
emotions and drawing people in with
storytelling I love storytelling and I
feel like I haven't even douve into that
at all because weddings has been my
version of storytelling now kind of
formulating how a day goes down and how
I want to portray that day but yeah as
of now I'm just kind of figure out what
I want just kind of like wearing a new
pair of clothes all the time
I mean I'll film myself podcasting I'll
film you've got a podcast and it's
starting up pretty soon yeah I'll uh
I'll film the podcast while talk it's
gonna be coming on pretty soon here I
like doing like mini documentary style
shoots nature shoots are one of my
favorite dude your nature stuff is super
beautiful
yeah wedding stuff is great too but yes
I like you and you have an eye they're
sure that seems to be everyone's
favorite so
far as the way I incorporate nature into
it and it's just my my job I guess what
I like to do so yeah cool dude that's
super exciting yeah I'm excited for that
for the future of our two companies or
two branches of whenever this is a
company seems like a great hour what is
technically for the people that don't
know what junkyard love is I wish I can
I'll pan around this room with my camera
one day and show you how cool it is
yeah I don't know dude it's so it
started I was like I'm just amuse I'm
deed I've been a DJ for eight years I've
this started it's like you know I'm
practicing down here this is a huge
basement of my home and it just turned
into like out putting more and more work
on it and then I just turned into my
creative studio essentially it's like a
kind of a recording studio I don't have
anything too crazy expensive at the
Scout got what we need for any sort of
like live recordings but it's also kind
of just a creative zone it's a it's a
it's a sanctuary down here for sure but
junk air love represents kind of all the
things that I have my hands in I'm
someone who's working on a little bit of
everything at once I'm just a general
creator it's kind of my way of jumping
out if I've been DJ Cronos for for so
many years and I felt a little boxed in
frankly by it and so I feel like
junqeira love is kind of just a way of
me expanding from being just a DJ and in
an audio engineer and kind of just being
a creative collective so I have podcasts
like life coaching motivational stuff
coming out of meditations guided
meditations I'm still gonna sneak some
DJ mixes in there I've I've been
learning to play a little bit of music
and work with a lot of bands so I said
yeah sorry it's just a little bit of
everything I'm just I just I'm a man of
novelty and in in fascination and
inspiration you know I just
I've I want to I don't know I guess mine
in the world and in mine creative
thought and and try to humanize and
relay in a realistic form what I'm
learning back to that damaged yeah I'm
trying to communicate it's okay it's a
lot of emotions but that's literally one
of the things that drew me to such a
strong bromance with you dude you are
like fearless when it comes to that
creative world there is such a stigma of
now if you're not necessarily like good
at something like you know a talented
musician or a talented DJ or whatever
the case may be
then you should not try to post it or
try it or you're not a singer don't sing
or things like that like you literally
take on everything as if you are the
world's greatest singer and you you
practice making music as if you know how
to make music I have to without without
any fear of judgment or anything like
that it's it's all for the love of
creativity and and pushing yourself to
see alright what else can I do and like
you can do these things that's what
people will come up to creative people
all the time and they'll say like I wish
I had your gifts like I really really
want to harness playing a guitar I
really want to harness like you just
shoot photos so good like I wish I can
take photos so that good you have an eye
for it yes some people do have an eye
for it yes some people are better than
others
but some people have better voices yes
but people don't try even if that sounds
garbage it's going to sound garbage at
first you're not gonna be Mozart when
you play the piano first you're gonna
suck you know you don't know if you can
play unless you play for a year or a
month or you know however long you want
to go for try if you don't enjoy it you
know that you don't enjoy that now
you know it's like yeah exactly you got
more you know either the more you know
the more you try the more you know
yourself right specifically what you do
and do not like just like food you have
to try everything like its food and know
that like alright music is somewhat like
green beans to me and I [__] hate
green beans like it's just not not tasty
to me but if you're like I don't know
let's try to eat green beans every day
for 30 days see if I really like green
beans and if not let's say alright I'll
write it down on a piece of paper I do
not agree beans forever but that's the
thing is like people don't know that
they don't like it until they've done it
for a while like like for the most part
like if I were to pick up a guitar and
try and play it
I don't immediately look at the guitar
and say I don't like playing you like I
don't even want to touch you you know
like you just don't sound good in my
hands like I don't enjoy the way you
make my fingers feel like like 90% of
people maybe a hundred percent don't
look at something go like I never want
to try that unless it's like bungee
jumping or something which I'm not down
for maybe but if I have any advice it's
literally literally if you are
fascinated in anything whatsoever you
have an inkling of yearning to do this
try it out try it try it out every
single day do it for 10 minutes 15
minutes every single day you'll realize
that you're getting better and you're
gonna snap one day and go oh my god
mm-hmm I'm actually like understanding
the fundamentals of this it's the
foundation for learning something and I
think knowledge and learning things is
the way that you continuously find joy
and happiness in life mm-hmm because
people are constantly searching for
happiness and they're like I can't find
it no matter what I do like I tried
going to the gym and I tried doing this
things these things are foundations for
you to live a healthy life in a happy
life but there are things that you need
to attain the the standard of having a
goal and setting out and going through
trials and tribulations to achieve that
goal is what keeps you happy and that's
what I tell people is like if they ask
me like you know you're so good like I
wish you I wish I had this talent pick
up the camera thank you yeah pick it
just pick it up and then take pictures
you my pick I'll show you my pictures
when I first started they were [__]
yeah dude they literally were [__] no
shooting I was shooting on auto auto
settings you know the camera was doing
all the work I wasn't even doing
anything
now I can now I understand a camera now
I can touch it and move it and adjust it
I know how to get a look I want like I
now know things that I never thought I
would know and it's it's brought me so
much joy and I think it'll bring a lot
of people joy dude I agree I think also
once you know something sitting at the
fact that you still don't know anything
like there's so many things like we're
talking about drones for example there's
so much that you you are probably
agreeably dude I know nothing about this
and some days like me with audio stuff
there's so much that I'm like I'm an
easy year I don't know anything about
monkey and yeah but but then there's
other things people like what is that
and then you got to remember like okay
there was a point where I didn't know
any of this was here in just just having
having the passion shooting your passion
towards that it's kind of like how you
fill in the blanks in between your life
and you realize that that that searching
in learning something new trying to look
for creative passions it's really a lot
of what what brings fulfillment to you
hurts did you what connects you to your
soul you know and whatever that might be
yeah it's that's the thing is that
everyone is constantly sorry everyone is
constantly looking ahead I mean I even
find myself doing it is when I'm working
on what I'm doing now I'm studying the
people that are ahead of me obviously
it's what you do you go into a karate
class you
watch your master you know teach you how
to do something so you can become better
but a lot of the times I'll get my
sights set on all I'm not that good you
know I'm not where I was but the past me
would look at me now and go holy [__] I
wish I was there
right whoa you know yeah think about you
as like an older brother yeah kind of a
cool thing to do like Haley always says
she always says like something wrong
lines I would think of like what 16 year
old you would would want and if you
think of yourself now you know as like
oh man I'm just the older brother of my
young self like oh should I have learned
a lot and but the thing is what stops
you from learning a lot is saying that's
not I don't know any I don't know how to
use a camera I don't know like oh I wish
I could do that like saying that that's
not for you saying that you can't do it
the thing about like that that's you
know I I want to outwardly be you know a
great gatekeeper breaker you know like
people thinking like I I can't play
piano because I'm not I'm not good like
it don't get on a stage and say I'm
really good and then suck like screw
stages get in your basement and just
play for hours and suck and suck and
then if you want to be good at
basketball go to your basketball hoop
outside and suck and miss 100 and then
maybe you're gonna make one but I think
the world of creativity is is if people
think it's like only for a certain type
of person you know and certainly there
is more people who are prone to certain
creative things certain people are just
magically wonderful at that at certain
things but they also love it so they do
it a lot but I just want it to be clear
I want to make sure everybody knows like
there's no gatekeepers the year you're
allowed to play music you're allowed to
draw you allowed to paint your life to
dance mm-hmm you're allowed to do yoga
and suck at it you're allowed to shoot
basketballs and suck at shooting those
you're allowed to do whatever you want
and suck at it don't lie don't lie to
anybody and say that you're good at it
don't don't don't try to compare
yourself and say that being good is even
what what the point is just feeling the
art of creating something
human is is easy it has it's important
yeah it's good yeah and it's supposed to
do that it's the difference between an
artist and someone who wants to create
art is the amount of time the artist
spends well the amount of time that the
creative person or the person that wants
to create dreams about spending you know
dreams about doing this the artist does
the creative person who wants to create
dreams they spend the same amount of
time I bet you they spend the same
amount of time doing and thinking one of
them just does so you have to be a doer
you have to spend the time it's it's so
exhausting sometimes it's late late
nights because you're so enthralled in
it and then it'll mess up your habits
and it'll throw you in a funk and your
head will be crazy and that's the bow
that is the Battle of being an artist
it's it's a lot of yeah yeah yeah and a
lot of people that aren't wholeheartedly
believing that they are a creative and a
creative person will drop out somewhere
along the along the lines they'll start
drowning and they'll give it up and say
even start if they even fully start and
so that's that's the thing it's time
it's if you want to be good at something
even the people who suck even if you
become good and you're just an average
guitarist from someone else's standard
who is a phenomenal guitar player we
started off just okay and it's now a
phenom the level of growth is still the
same you have become a suck guitar
player to an average mediocre pretty
good knows how to play songs and can
play the guitar that amount of growth is
amazing that's it's phenomenal and it
should give you
you get most joy knowing that like still
like okay I'm not the best I aspire to
be just like him you know or just like
whoever is playing the guitar and
shredding it like that
I can't do that at the moment but the
amount of growth that I've done and
knowing this satisfaction that I can
strum on this thing and I can make music
is so satisfying Tim to me a normal
person I would love to play the guitar a
normal person yeah I feel like a normal
person at the moment everybody feels
like a normal person no I don't even the
people who are like you're like you're
so gifted they're just they're serious
when they're like I don't know I just
don't pick up the thing and just but I
don't know I'm just so I'm not gifted
you know like they're like that nervous
sort of whatever it's true about
everyone man like nobody really I mean
maybe some people's egos think they are
but they could
nobody really feels like you're just a
person yeah just a person dude it just
in creating is something a person can do
you know and everyone's allowed to do it
and I just think that yeah I mean it's I
think something that we're gonna do
together with a lot of the stuff that
we're creating and and that we're
working on together with just super
exciting stuff is a is gonna show a lot
of people I hope it shows a lot of
people like you're allowed to create you
know yeah I think you're allowed to
express yeah you're allowed to be
inspired by whatever's around you and
you're allowed to you know what we
should do is we should say if you happen
to be listening this podcast how about
for the next week you make a rule to
yourself that you don't say I don't do
that or I'm not good at that so if
someone's like hey do you want to cover
and paint later you can't say I suck at
painting you're not allowed to say I
suck anything I don't do that I suck at
that therefore I'm not going to do it so
if something comes up and there's an
opportunity to do something in the next
seven days listening or if there are no
opportunities create an opportunity to
do something outside of the box and just
tell yourself hey like my parents gave
me a guitar last summer maybe I'll
practice that for 20 minutes or maybe I
feel like I suck at painting so I'll
invite some friends over or
sit and paint by myself and like have no
judgments and just paint whatever I want
to try and look up a picture online and
see if you can paint it or just whatever
the case may be just doing something
that you would throws you off your
everyday is going to jumpstart something
creative within your body it's going to
give you some serious happiness because
I know changing up the mundane routine
even if your routine is so cool to
someone else it becomes mundane to you
like if you ran every morning and you
lifted and you came home and you cooked
two eggs and you you know get all this
stuff if you did it every single day
you're gonna be like dude like I'm like
yes I do feel good I'm happy that I do
this I kick ass but at the same time
sometimes you want something a little
different yeah so I be creative hold
that yeah I hope that people just try
something out of the box so that it'll
give them some sort of jumpstart to to
whatever it is and if it's the gym go
hit the gym because I love the gym or
stop in the gym actual that's right with
me is I had been working out for so or
stop I had like I had gone through waves
of just loving the gym I would hang out
bunch of body builders I would get big
get small get kind of tubby big and then
I stopped go to the gym but and started
doing my yoga stuff and I imagine for
like a year
mm-hmm so yeah just just switching it up
but you're just not not not you're
switching up an in pursuit of health I
was like it just wasn't feeling right it
wasn't getting what I needed it you know
to give me I mean so I started pursuing
something that felt better which was
yoga working out at home running running
around here trail running stuff you did
some trail running the other day that's
fun ooh that was a wild fun that is
trail running is certainly cool dude
what that's the crazy thing trail
running what do you think about that
it's got to be super primitive right
that kind of I compared it to if you're
a skier diamond in and out of trees
right you're you're Hessian and you
don't see the trees at all you only see
your path you only see the one white
everything else is a blur
oh yeah you know you're scared yeah but
the trees are just zoom trail running
feels kind of like dude you're only on
the path it's like going through space
like you're going through this weird
like path of space that's drawn out for
you and there but there's something
super primitive about it like there's
something innately inside that like yes
it is tough and yes it's physically
challenging but it brings some sort of
peace and some sort of like rhythmic
movement in your body it's a flow state
that feels especially trail running and
being out in nature and stuff you almost
get connected to the trail itself and
your flow where the trail and you become
one and then suddenly you become one
with everything because you're you're in
balance you're literally balancing
around curves and bends up downs
yeah you're just very quickly throwing
your body weight around I mean it's kind
of strategic you know you know it's like
the one we did you get to spot through
there's puddles or there's or those
places where you got to suddenly slow
down to cross a narrow little bridge
thing like it's not difficult but slow
down and then speed back up but you're
also turning and so you know we'll all
notice parts when we did it we put like
our foot up up like a the two feet up
high out on a rock wall or something you
know foot up high and kind of just like
move our whole body weight just so
quickly you know we don't know this
trail but it just seems like it's you
know it's pretty cool to just notice
like how much you can haul ass through
the woods when you have it open like
dude it's like and we are actually
badass but it's because you know we used
to that's how we would get through is a
deer can help sprint us but we can
outrun him in longevity so we would just
keep it going probably flow state do we
probably chases [__] for miles
for sure there's no doubt they're like
running like God
well have you got the thing is they give
up you're like they're like I don't do
it I probably would to like you just
spare me already give me any good spots
maybe like into beef jerky or something
yeah so I'm not sure keep deer jerky
yeah I bet you up so good they just
accept life because they're like well
they're gonna love my mmm-hmm anyway we
trailed off into the death of a deer
yeah see you dude somehow it gets there
yeah we got from like skinny jeans to
two deer death dude it's really it's
like for like four hours
I knew that we argue we are the
algorithm that suggests new videos and
new content as I bet you we are cuz I
literally am like I'll type in like some
camera stuff and then next thing you
know I'm on like prehistoric dinosaurs
and like why the earth is flat and stuff
and I am just like how we're dinosaurs
on a flat earth but it's so interesting
right it slices fake the first steps of
the podcast hey by the way listeners if
you don't believe that the earth is flat
you're crazy
yeah and we're gonna have half the half
the fan group just like leave
immediately and and the other one and
the other half is gonna stick around for
like just to see what's going on I think
he has a crazy where is this going
yeah I feel like the crazier you sound
the actual like more engagement you get
so I'm good if nothing works for us here
let's just start talking space is fake
and like just absurd [__] I mean all
right hold up how do you know space is
real cuz I've been there I've been that
high well okay but that's the young
interns in the space you have been space
I you have become space been spacey
space and space the [__] out yeah in
class I've been space now for sure but
you have no way of proving it except for
hopefully the people at NASA
are telling us the truth and things like
that which is just a whole nother topic
of like how do you know that smart
people and scientists and everything are
literally telling you the truth
like everyone innately just believes
everything mm-hmm that like a scientist
may say more like some like known facts
you know what I mean like but like so
many people are so quick to just put a
[__] microwave in your house and like
throw food in it and like if I ask you
like what is the microwave do how does
it work
it heats it up with radio waves no it
doesn't it it yeah it grabs the
watermark molecules and shakes him up so
fast that that they become hot and then
your food gets hot and then that's it
which is [__] crazy why don't we have
that I feel like we shouldn't kind of
have control I would seem so nuts you
can cook something in a minute but
literally I mean it is safe and and
there are no nothing that's causing you
to have like cancer or any chemical
waves that are positive or molecular
molecular structure structure structures
let's say structure mycelia cool ooh
okay cool yeah I mean they didn't lie
about that you know they were honest
with that but just a simple fact of
saying like if someone presents you with
knowledge so many people are so quick
Facebook quick to be like in fact like
that's a [__] fact I'm gonna die with
this [__] no and I'm like dude well I
don't know if this is real I don't know
well that's the thing is I mean if you
really want to extend it I mean so it's
so I've gone down rabbit holes on
YouTube yeah of just watching this guy
leo Gura sounds a correct actualised on
that like he's pulled it up from your
butthole no but like he essentially sits
there and talks for two hours about like
what is truth what's real like what's
truth of reality or whatever
it's and it's like oh [__] like the way
that we believe everything is just like
alright well so you read that and I'm
like uh-huh any like you sure you read
that like mm-hmm you're like where'd you
read it like it was it was a is a book
then it's right in your like okay I mean
it's just that's the thing though is you
know outside of language outside of you
know like what words are on paper and
the sentence as it in as it is all back
to the root of that what truth really is
is is you gotta feel it you've got to be
like I know this to be true I know this
to be right and that's how that's what
started truth you know it seems like
anyway it seems like that's the birth of
truth is is is you know not just your
your gut feeling as we know it but but
your truth innately you know each have
our own so it's weird I I think that's
what's so ingrained in our society about
creativity and why we are so so
attracted to creating and creating art
because I believe art at it's very core
is truth like if I if you were to play a
song and you show the keys and why you
played that there's there's truth behind
it you know there's like there's this
sound and these keys will make that
sound it is true it's known that this
will make that you know and and it's a
way to discover that and and it's
specific between every every other
person that's why it's so like oh oh
that's what you see is your truth and
that's what you see when you're playing
this is like so profound it's so amazing
and that's what's so enticing but that's
why I think so many people are drawn to
creativity it's it's there's no sort of
like BS behind it there's no sort of
like I don't know is that true like I
feel like that might have been a
different key you played and you're just
lying to me no that's this is if I say
an a-minor like that's what an a-minor
sounds like and like you can play it too
yeah
I mean it'll somebody found that last
some like dumb ape who had a rock in his
hand like eventually his lineage that
was somebody there learned like huh
what's that did you imagine it's
discovered he finds a minor with a
rabbit 5 and just [__] EDC like
turntable with rocks yes there's there's
literally seven people in the audience
there's so many that you can't even get
in seven whole people because which
looks just like EDC oh yeah I was just
grabbing 2017 yeah hey did you hear that
pop right then yeah I did okay so that's
something I think it's my headphone
amplifier and it's terrifying and I
think that it turns my fight-or-flight
on Oh Kitson definitely not that
recording but uh just a little side note
for me so dang I just broke the third
wall that's like it is that's the crazy
thing so that's cool
I was just mentioning our headphones and
when you're in headphones I feel like
you kind of lock into this like double
flow state of like podcasting yeah we're
like in depth with this conversation
yeah but then I mentioned the headphones
and it felt like I was like oh yeah like
real life like for a second started
hearing the sounds out here yeah like
your focus it's kind of interesting how
our focus goes and when you're having
like genuinely intellect you know
perhaps not the last thing we're talking
about
yeah the conversation that we started
with spaces is it real yeah I know you
know you do kind of lock into it but but
a it's interesting I feel like that's a
good step so as we were locked in here
all right we're having this conversation
like we're kind of in like this flow
state of conversation I'm building up
what you're saying I'm not checking my
phone whatever whatever I'm hearing what
you're hearing your hearing when I'm
I think that's what's so important about
podcasts - it's like I feel like ivory
learned what conversation is due to a
podcast and it is extremely daunting it
is very scary like just to even be on
the spot with someone because there's so
many times when I have like awkward
exchanges and I'm talking to someone and
the conversation literally goes nowhere
and it's like both of us are understand
so on where do I think sometimes you're
trying or throwing things like hey how
is Mary Ann your doctor man both of you
literally will go like like off into
your own zone and then you'll snap and
like do that weird like fake thing like
you were saying like well how's your
kids by the way or like yeah your job
it's a loop yeah and it's like jobs good
do the same thing boom I mean it's like
I'm not even having conversation at this
point like I almost want to say like
dude we're not having good convo right
now and we should come back to this
another day yeah good you know I mean
okay seriously though I mean I am a man
who you know believe it or not for how
much I'm often blabbing but there's a
there's a moments there's days there's a
week sometimes months where I really
prefer silence maybe not months that's
intense but like I'm saying I think it
would be cool if there's a time where
you committing this conversation is
going to where you can exchange a look
glance and you both sit in silence for
the next hour mm-hmm like and enjoy it
though not like oh my gosh this date is
so awkward and you retreat to your phone
to talk about how terrible your
situation is right now instead of
experiencing it yeah but yeah no I think
that which I can't believe for right
the importance of podcasting manage is
crazy because I think me like I was
always a pretty confident exuberant like
I was an actor growing up like yeah
young like I enjoyed I wasn't so much
outwardly like extroverted but there was
things where I'm like I'm good at
like I had a you know salesman jobs when
I was 16 like I remember the interview
like suddenly should be like sell me
this pen she handed it to me
oh [__] and I killed it you know I was
like oh yeah of course
you know but I would I would sell it
like I would tell about the things of
the pen but anyway so I would be good at
speaking I'd be good at situations I was
always good at observing the other
person and seeing what kind of situation
it like what type what part of Jake what
type of my chameleon personality needs
to match the situation right well in
house I became like you know more
depressed and more like it's just sucked
into social media do you know all these
things in my life I began to like lose
those let's say abilities of like human
interaction and whatever but so I
started like would hang out myself which
I was more comfortable that way but I
would start watching YouTube's the
youtubes podcast and stuff people are
talking back and forth and I started
watching eye contact and I started
realizing like man I don't do that I
don't want to do that I'm very
uncomfortable around people I look at my
my feet I wasn't always like this so it
gave me this like just because I wasn't
always like this I was like this is
weird I don't want to be this person who
can't make eye contact you can have
conversations who is so afraid of losing
my train of thought in the middle of my
thought that I don't even talk to
anybody so I think that you almost have
to get it back and I think that social
media and the way that we talk to you al
e.x a I won't say you know cuz she'll
start going I want to say Lord her the
more same because there's one same
excess but a but I think that the way
that automation and weird stuff like
with technology and just us being sucked
on our phone the way we type in shorten
things language and a lot of our our
speaking abilities and looking to other
the eye stuff like that
communicating ourselves in communicating
what we're trying to [__] say mm-hmm
it has been really pushed away and in
the last few years in the last you know
since the iPhone came out let's just say
yeah so I think that a podcast really
helped like special especially
get the visual of them they help people
understand conversations and help listen
I've already improved my listening
skills I've already like I listened to
the first couples at grey house
interrupting a lot you know you learn a
lot from podcasting but also you I mean
you learn a lot regardless but I like
the way that like you're locked in and
the only thing that I can hear is you
the only thing you can hear is me and
the only thing that we're seeing is each
other yeah and it just provides this
like just almost like confined like
secluded box of just like me to you you
to me and there's nothing else but that
and that whole focus of like it's almost
like going to practice like talking like
if you were to go to like a karate class
for like talking in like well [__] bro
it's totally that and you know what I
mean like yeah I feel like we just like
hacked it's like people are gonna listen
to us talk and weren't like we're just
practicing like we're just getting good
because so you know yeah the being good
at conversation and being good at
talking and in understanding and
listening is very it's a tool that you
have to sharpen mmm for sure
it's so you know like we're gonna get
good at this and I feel like we're
stealing from the world now yeah and I
feel like your voice is the most
attractive thing about you as an
individual I think it can be used in
ways that are more powerful than
anything that you can do physically
because if you look at people who are
insanely talented and have incredible
music abilities they get looked at as
this artist but I've seen people who are
that and then have this amazing voice
and can project themselves in a way in
which they talk and can express
themselves as a person and not an artist
is just like I respect them more for
them as a as a individual and as a
person than for their art itself I see
them as a person and not just this kind
of figment of people's imagination you
know because like if I were to meet
didn't like post Malone or something
like I only know him for his music right
and and like people only know me now for
my video and photo skills like anytime I
meet anyone that I know or that know of
me in a way they people want to have
conversation with you if you obviously
see them and you know them and the first
thing they're gonna say is I'll do it I
love your camera [__] or I'll dude I
love the way you take pictures mm-hmm
that's crazy to me
like you literally are like looking at
me for my skill and like you're looking
at me as an artist and like you're
trying to talk through to me from my
creative self like well I'm just kind of
kicking it and like being my normal self
like my creative self and my normal self
is very different my mind my mindset is
different my tenacity for creating is
different and it's you're talking to a
different person that's why I gave
myself a different persona of Zakk Wylde
as being that because when I step into
that state that's when I can become that
part of me right when I'm Brandon I'm
I'm just a normal guy trying to have a
good conversation with someone which yes
I can talk about that but people look to
you just like people look to comedians
to make them laugh on the street right
you know what I mean you're a clown fish
aren't you funny yeah exactly exactly
like no like I saw Kevin Hart on a
podcast and he's like dude like everyone
comes up to me and expect me to make
them laugh and weird and like I'm not
funny all the time you literally said
it's like I'm not funny all the time I
can't be funny all the time I would lose
my sense of funniness I would 24 hours a
day like I have wheels I might it was
like a me exactly exactly like I'm not
gonna [__] scratch everywhere I go and
like create a [__] little rave for
you for everyone walking down the
streets the thing is is
the way that we talk to each other the
way that we label each other the way
that we like see like here's who you are
is your job you know your thing what you
do that brings in money is who you are
and it's like wait hold up but I'm a lot
more like like and that's creative
people understand that you know that's
why that's why they make aliases like so
aliases in the avatars to to be in the
world I mean that's it seems psychotic
to so many people but it makes so much
sense when they're when you're doing it
yourself and like so many people have
asked me like like I literally don't
understand why you call yourself that
like are you crazy or like are you like
like I don't get it that that seems like
some sort of self-defense thing or like
some sort of thing that you don't want
to present yourself as you know Brandon
because you're afraid to be branded
something like that you know it's like
no like I'm separating my creative self
and and a version of myself in which I
have to slip into a different mindset
and a different being basically to
accomplish this goal versus me just
being myself right yeah I've tried to be
seen as dude yeah that it reminds me I
had this gig one time where they they
put like well it's more than once this
happens more than once but this made
when they put like on a billboard letter
board thing like DJ grinds and I was
like I created Cronos so I so I could
just have that alias and I can live like
that yeah and it's it's hard because you
kind of want to separate I can't want to
talk about music all the time sometimes
just want to chill I'm thinking okay how
are you like do you know did you I don't
know I mean I mean the same thing with
you like it like it seems cool that they
recognize you as your artistry at first
yeah it's very cool which is great in
that you know I don't think there's
anything wrong with that I think you
know if that's the way that if you're
like I don't know how to approach this
person but I think they're really cool
I'm gonna use this as an in way like hey
man I really like your photography
whatever or whatever but then realize
that like
hey this is also a human like you love
his art you just told him that like
that's so cool but now like just talk to
him no yeah he's just he's just a dude
like you know he also has emotions and
feelings yeah it seems like like I know
everyone's intentions are good and they
want to spark conversation and get to
know someone who's kind of trying to
follow their goals and dreams and stuff
but they kind of like go down the
YouTube rabbit hole of like not changing
topics and things like that and it's
like alright well you take pictures and
it's like oh what about this and what
about this and you think you create this
and then ultimately at least my friends
are looking to get into this and we need
we hope that you can help us with like
free videos that way maybe one day we'll
hit you up for family photos or whatever
the case may be and and then it's like
bye
which has happened like a billion
billion times I just got robbed yeah and
I'm like I actually wanted to talk to
you and see like what's going on like my
flaw is like I don't go on social media
enough to see like what's going on in
people's lives so when I actually see
people like I'm curious to know what
what you've been doing yeah
like how's your baby and you got to have
a cool I'll literally I'll literally
talk to people and be like like what is
new not like work school no like what
like what have you done like did you
have like a game night the other night
did you go on a crazy ass hike like like
what what has happened did you go out
and just get shit-faced on Saturday or
what like yeah who are you and what do
you do well I think that you know even
expanding on just that sentence there I
think that all of our conversation in
the Western world should change to like
this like hey how are you good I'm good
good in like how's work going you still
have the same job yeah I'm still Lola
like with our work is our first base
level of communication which we haven't
talked about a million times before I
feel like I don't know what the answer
is and I feel like a lot of our friend
group style you know we have a good way
of breaking through that [__] just
talking like here oh it's good to see
you anyway but like we go right into it
but on this
you know we do have to interact with
people we don't know every day but I
don't think we need to have this like
super fake like just trying to meet each
other and know each other really quickly
through our work that's like it already
paints us in this false like because a
lot of people so like when I meet people
people are like oh you're DJ they think
it's like this cool like I'm trying to
be famous I'm trying to be this a cool
thing and then they just work at you
know a bank let's say and so when they
talk to me I'm like hey how are you
what's good oh I'm pretty good you know
just working on the bank you know so I
think like they they downplay their life
because they compare their life to mine
assuming that like the DJ life is just
wonderful or whatever yeah
don't know if that's exactly what
they're thinking yeah but but it seems
insane man yeah essentially I just I
don't the way that we say like our first
interaction should never be like this
person's job is better than mine so I'm
gonna insult my job and I'm also not my
job yeah I'm gonna downplay it because
I'm not accomplishing the same goals as
them and things like that and like we
should talk about happiness yeah what
percentage happiness have you been in
the last six months I'm like at 1500
that's not super good what's going on
yeah have you know yeah and if you talk
to creatives they say the same thing
like dude I'm like haven't been on my
parole for like two months like I feel
like I can't even like the stuff that
I'm creating people may like actually be
liking it and like what I'm putting out
with it I personally am like dude I'm
going crazy like trying to edit these
wedding videos or I'm going crazy trying
to do all this stuff because it's so
time-consuming and I literally feel like
I'm by myself for like 15 hours of the
mic I need to go outside and I need to
talk to someone
yeah but all you see is the end result
of my [__] madness you're like you
know in England they're like oh it's
this talent like you were born with just
this wonderful talent and you can just
like you just know exactly what to do is
like yeah because I spent all this time
like so it's hard to mine you know yeah
it's definitely a trick that's why I
want to make that I'm gonna be making a
documentary soon no I was like
talk about it yeah I'm making a
documentary about creatives and the
artists way of life from a mental
standpoint obviously showing what they
can do but more on the lines of what it
takes to become an artist and what kind
of goes down in people's lives behind
the scenes so you have an idea it's
super dope that you're like you're doing
that like because you've explained like
you're like this documentary you're
working on like pretty and depth to me
and I think it's super-important like
you've you're such a good listener too
like there's already been nights where
we got like a little bit of footage and
and we've had conversations where like
you've drawn me to explain myself in
ways that I'm like oh wow that's like a
really good way and and I think that
that like your work a lot of stuff that
you're doing is going to really help I
hate him in saying the sense because it
goes against what I said earlier but
like you know creatives and not in non
creative people who consider themselves
not creative who don't try to understand
like the emotional states of creative
people a lot of like the the traumatic
experiences that give way to a lot of
creations right you are really good at
pulling out and I think portraying in a
visual sense like the the plain English
love of what that mean cuz it's what
we're saying here is we're explaining
feelings with just words and feelings
are so much more powerful than words and
so you're explaining like the feelings
and the real emotions of of what it
takes to like hey that thing that you
love so much it took someone reaching
inside their heart and ripping it out
for like four hours a day for 16 months
to give you that thing yeah so like yeah
I think just it's important to mine the
way that with that way that we process
things and create things and you pull it
out well well so I'm excited man I
appreciate that it's gonna be it's gonna
be a journey I mean it's gonna take a
while and and just to gather emotion
from people just to break people's walls
down I mean I want to meet with people
who
are obviously creatives in different
fields but a lot of people I won't even
know and so to try and pull out some
sort of just intimate emotion and
feeling from someone I mean that I can't
just go grab my camera and say hey I
need you to like tell me about your past
in like you know explain like I listen
to the song and you were like almost
sounded like you were in tears over it
like what is the meaning behind that it
was like some people have some [__]
going on you know like some people have
literally been like beaten and molested
as kids and when that gives way to a
sense of relief when they create music
and or when they write poetry or
whatever the case may be
glassblowing or pottery or whatever it
is right it's something a lot of the
time I figured it's something pretty
traumatic or it's something that just
really left a mark on their lives and so
I mean I bet even with you like it once
we get into this like there's gonna be
some things that I have no idea about
that you may express and I have to have
responsibility for that I know better
no I have to have responsibility for
that and that is it's a very scary thing
but it's something that I hope I can
portray in the correct way and in a way
that is it really catches the eyes of
the viewer but also if it's you I hope
that's what emotion you're trying to
relay to yourself and everyone else
right so that's that's what I'm looking
for in this documentary is to try and
master the art of giving everyone what
they want in a sense that is really
beneficial for everyone in understanding
what it takes to be an artist it's super
important man I mean it's it's cool I
mean you I have no idea how long it may
take you it may be it's gonna take as
long as it takes for sure but I'm truly
honored that you're that you're putting
me in
and thanks and that feels pretty cool
just being conscious of your time here
you're a very busy man you're always
keeping yourself busy busy and motivated
with tons of work so you do have to get
going here pretty soon
so but before then do you want to
mention anything else was there any
other subject you want to make sure we
touch on on this on this first episode
of our little collab then we're gonna be
doing it oh man I think not because once
we start with one topic I literally
don't care what it is I have in life
I'll just keep going and like I'm in a
conversation here like I don't care if I
have to go to work or anything I'm like
dude yeah we're talking about you know
it's so funny we call you later
we just get so sidetracked but though
you know again those are important
conversations happen yeah got it got me
and we're gonna we got to save some save
some data for the next one but that's
what I love about talking he was like I
literally feel like we no matter how
many times we've talked for hours and
hours and hours and hours and never have
we been like alright we ran out of
things to say here like well like it's
all of a sudden I walk in the morning
you're like do I have to drive home and
I'm sleep-talking right now seriously
like it's just crazy it's it's so cool
though I mean that's yeah yeah dude I
appreciate you a lot yeah yeah you'll be
back soon
I just want to say I think probably our
next one if not our one after that our
next podcast together will likely be
perhaps outside that idea so hiking
would yeah so that should be pretty
integrate we get we get talking about
you know fairly important subjects on
the phone hikes and stuff so we kind of
wanted to maybe start recording that and
maybe we can get some get to the core
some more important things so anyway
podcast podcast out man
junkyard love thank you brother
you